export const questions=[
{
	question: "Smallest country in the world",
	answer1: "Monaco",
	answer2: "Marshall Islands",
	answer3: "Vatican City",
	answer4: "San Marino",
	correct: "Vatican City"

},
{
	question: "Least densely populated country",
	answer1: "Bhutan",
	answer2: "Greenland",
	answer3: "Australia",	
	answer4: "Namibia",
	correct: "Greenland"

},
{
	question: "Most linguistically diverse nation",
	answer1: "Solomon Islands",
	answer2: "Tanzania",	
	answer3: "Vanuatu",
	answer4: "Papua New Guinea",
    correct: "Papua New Guinea"
},
{
	question: "Which country produces the most amount of oxygen",
	answer1: "Russia",
	answer2: "Iceland",
	answer3: "Canada",	
	answer4: "Finland",
    correct: "Russia"
},
{
	question: "Country with least number of rivers",
	answer1: "Maldives",
	answer2: "Oman",
	answer3: "Saudi Arabia",
	answer4: "Qatar",
    correct: "Saudi Arabia"
},
{
	question: "Only country where Gross Domastic Happiness(GDH) is measured instead of GDP",
	answer1: "Nepal",
    answer2: "Bhutan",
	answer3: "China",	
	answer4: "Japan",
    correct: "Bhutan"
},
{
	question: "Country which has the most number of lakes in the world",
	answer1: "India",
	answer2: "Russia",	
	answer3: "Finland",
	answer4: "Canada",
    correct: "Canada"
},
{
	question: "Driest country in the world",
	answer1: "Libya",
	answer2: "Egypt",
	answer3: "Chile",	
	answer4: "Peru",
    correct: "Libya"
},
{
	question: "Culturally, Economically, Climatically , racially, Liguistically , ethnically and religiously The most diverse country in the world",
	answer1: "Uganda",
	answer2: "Liberia",	
	answer3: "Tanzania",
	answer4: "India",
    correct: "India"
},
{
	question: "The largest island in the world",
	answer1: "Baffin Island",
	answer2: "GreenLand",
	answer3: "Madagascar",	
	answer4: "New Guinea",
    correct: "GreenLand"
}
];



















